<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cat Arsenal</title>
    <link>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cat Arsenal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 11:49:02 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First Time Water Fx</title>
      <link>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/first-time-water-fx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 11:49:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/first-time-water-fx/</guid>
      <description>Working on a beach base for a bandai shore trooper figure wanted to try out vallejo water fx to simulate the water going up the shore. I’d previously seen tutorials on how to make water scenes however didn’t look specifically a tutorial with that specific product, the kind of tutorials i found were using a two part resin. I came to find out that using vallejo water fx is different and I think for particular situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 22:04:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Jess and I am a Prop And Modelkit Maker, I create Scratch build models, props and custom collectibles.
Recently I got more interested in dioramas and props for action figures so that they have a better display and also I’m trying out toy photography with the stuff I build.
You can contact me or find out what I&amp;rsquo;m working on here:
kira.navarro@gmail.com
Instagram</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Millenium Falcon</title>
      <link>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/millenium-falcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 12:17:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/millenium-falcon/</guid>
      <description>We found this Hasbro Millenium Falcon from the Solo movie for really cheap and I wanted to do something really quick just to make it look even more used, I only used MIG dark wash on all the ship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eva 02 Sculpt</title>
      <link>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/eva-02-sculpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 11:58:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/eva-02-sculpt/</guid>
      <description>This was sculpted in an oil based clay and then molded and casted in resin.
To paint this sculpt I sprayed a base coat of silver paint and then masked and airbrushed the red sections.
I really struggled in painting this one, I used Tamiya red transparent which has a weird consistency, it is a bit more thicker and sticky than the other paints, so what I learned from this is to add just a bit of water to the paint, only about 2 or 3 drops, and also spray small amounts of paint at a time because this paint dries even faster and it clogs the airbrush pretty fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trollhunters Amulet</title>
      <link>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/trollhunters-amulet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 17:51:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/trollhunters-amulet/</guid>
      <description>I made a pattern in illustrator, you can download the pattern for free here: Trollhunters amulet blueprint.
Made the basic shape out of Sintra and for the details I mostly used two part epoxy putty to be able to sculpt detail runes all the way round. For the amulets base I created a two part mold, and the castings where roto-casted however this didn&amp;rsquo;t work very well, since it was very dificult to keep a consistent thikness thougout all the piece, I actually ended up filling up the rim sides with epoxy putty after I casted the piece so that I could have a more solid piece to work on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones Coasters</title>
      <link>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/game-of-thrones-coasters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 17:25:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/game-of-thrones-coasters/</guid>
      <description>For this x-mas I wanted to give to my siblings something they really like, so I decided to make this coasters of their favorite show.
I first made a master coaster by cutting out the basic shapes out of sintra, then with a sculpting tool I engraved the wood texture glued the pieces together, and added little punched styrene circles to simulate rivets of some kind, then primed and sanded the piece.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inquisitor Helmet</title>
      <link>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/inquisitor-helmet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 22:06:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/inquisitor-helmet/</guid>
      <description>This is one of my first builds made with EVA foam, I followed Evil Ted’s video tutorial, and got the template for free also from his site here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poe Dameron’s X-Wing</title>
      <link>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/poe-dameron-xwing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 21:55:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/poe-dameron-xwing/</guid>
      <description>Got the new Poe Dameron’s Black X-Wing but when I opened it surprise! it is not black lol, so I have to give this guy a new paint job. I first turned everything apart so that It’s easier for me to paint.
*Note: Take a lot of pictures or a video while doing this so that when it is time to put it all together you know how to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Force Awakens Trooper Blaster</title>
      <link>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/force-awakens-trooper-blaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 10:44:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/force-awakens-trooper-blaster/</guid>
      <description>We got this awesome Storm trooper Nerf gun, and after looking at Bill Doran’s video thought I would give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>