<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scratch Build on Cat Arsenal</title>
    <link>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/tags/scratch-build/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scratch Build on Cat Arsenal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 17:51:35 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/tags/scratch-build/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trollhunters Amulet</title>
      <link>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/trollhunters-amulet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 17:51:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/trollhunters-amulet/</guid>
      <description>I made a pattern in illustrator, you can download the pattern for free here: Trollhunters amulet blueprint.
Made the basic shape out of Sintra and for the details I mostly used two part epoxy putty to be able to sculpt detail runes all the way round. For the amulets base I created a two part mold, and the castings where roto-casted however this didn&amp;rsquo;t work very well, since it was very dificult to keep a consistent thikness thougout all the piece, I actually ended up filling up the rim sides with epoxy putty after I casted the piece so that I could have a more solid piece to work on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones Coasters</title>
      <link>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/game-of-thrones-coasters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 17:25:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kiraproject.net/catarsenal/posts/game-of-thrones-coasters/</guid>
      <description>For this x-mas I wanted to give to my siblings something they really like, so I decided to make this coasters of their favorite show.
I first made a master coaster by cutting out the basic shapes out of sintra, then with a sculpting tool I engraved the wood texture glued the pieces together, and added little punched styrene circles to simulate rivets of some kind, then primed and sanded the piece.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>